export const englishQuestions = [
  {
    question: 'What is the meaning of "accept"?',
    options: ['受け入れる', '受け取る', '期待する', '交換する'],
    answer: '受け入れる',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the meaning of "benefit"?',
    options: ['罰', '保証', '手段', '利益'],
    answer: '利益',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the meaning of "challenge"?',
    options: ['選択', '挑戦', '反省', '決定'],
    answer: '挑戦',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the meaning of "depend"?',
    options: [ '避ける', '繰り返す', '頼る', '超える'],
    answer: '頼る',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the meaning of "environment"?',
    options: ['装置', '環境', '制度', '機会'],
    answer: '環境',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the meaning of "feature"?',
    options: ['物語', '結果', '特徴', '課題'],
    answer: '特徴',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the meaning of "global"?',
    options: ['地域の', '伝統的な', '個人的な' , '世界的な'],
    answer: '世界的な',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the meaning of "increase"?',
    options: ['増える', '減る', '止まる', '分ける'],
    answer: '増える',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the meaning of "material"?',
    options: ['材料', '速度','目的', '地位', ],
    answer: '材料',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the meaning of "prevent"?',
    options: ['防ぐ', '許す', '望む', '届ける'],
    answer: '防ぐ',
  }
];
